[
  {
    "QuestionText": "Which is the largest ocean?",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Pacific",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
      "Atlantic",
      "Indian",
      "Misssissippi",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionText": "Who starts first in chess?",
    "CorrectAnswer": "White",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
      "Black",
      "Me",
      "White"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionText": "What year did Elvis Presley Die",
    "CorrectAnswer": "1977",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
      "1978",
      "1843",
      "He's still alive!",
      "1977"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionText": "Who is the main actor in 'Cocktail'?",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Tom Cruise",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
      "Tom Hanks",
      "Tom Cruize",
      "Vincent Nguyen",
      "Tom Cruise"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionText": "Where does the American president live?",
    "CorrectAnswer": "The White House",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
      "Washington Monument",
      "Mexico",
      "Des Moinese, IA",
      "The White House"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionText": "Which river goes through London",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Thames",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
      "Pacific",
      "Nile",
      "Amazon",
      "Thames"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionText": "Who sang 'My Way'?",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Frank Sinatra",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
      "Tom Cruize",
      "Rihanna",
      "Andrew Damon",
      "Frank Sinatra"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionText": "How many prongs are there on a fork",
    "CorrectAnswer": "4",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "5",
      "6",
      "7",
      "8",
      "9",
      "o",
      "4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionText": "What is the only mammal that can't jump",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Elephant",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
      "Human",
      "Rat",
      "Telephone",
      "Elephant"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionText": "What company are you interning at?",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Buildertrend",
    "IncorrectAnswers": [
      "Shell",
      "Amazon",
      "Tesla",
      "Buildertrend"
    ]
  }
]